(Leonard(pulling out a toy lightsabre):)You call that a glow stick?
(Leonard(pulling out a toy lightsabre):)That is a glow stick.
Come on, Iet's go.
Before you go, consider this:
(Sheldon:)Not only do I have a deep-cycle
marine battery power source...
(Sheldon:)...more than capable of running
our entertainment system...
(Sheldon:)...I also have all 61 episodes
of the BBC series Red Dwarf.
And Fiddle Faddle.
(Sheldon:)All yours if you're willing to reinstate
the Roommate Agreement.
(Penny:)I've got wine at my place
and some bubble wrap we could pop.
(Sheldon:)He'll be back. Wine and a girl in the dark,
he's gonna be bored out of his mind.
(Leonard:)To wine and bubble wrap.
(Leonard:)And to not having to watch Sheldon
demonstrate his reverse-osmosis machine...
(Leonard:)...that converts urine into drinking water.